Leigh Warner

CONTACT

128 Donomore Ave,

Dublin 24

E-mail: leighwarner3@gmail.com **Website:** https://github.com/LeighWarner99,

https://www.linkedin.com/in/leigh-warner-/

Phone: 0858486800

PROFILE

Recent graduate from Technological University Dublin, where I obtained my degree in Computer Science with Data Analytics. Acquired my knowledge and experience from working on projects while attending college and my internship. Vast knowledge of programming languages, OS troubleshooting, cloud technologies, and database languages. I am extremely excited to join a workplace and bring my skills and knowledge to a company and further my expertise in the field.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Electrical Supply Board

January 2020 — August 2020

Enterprise Services

- Provide constant feedback/support to manager about day to day tasks.
- Engaged in weekly meetings, where I got involved with the project.
- Automating day to day tasks with the use of PowerShell.
- Point of contact for users who wish to create new user accounts through the MDMS database.
- Using SQL scripts to obtain information about new incoming meters, analyzing the information and corresponding with my team to identify the correct information was relayed.
- Maintain a clean working environment during my time.
- Used my time in my internship to branch out and network.

MR Price

July 2022 — Present

Sales Assistant

- Confidently manage an EPOS system, handling various transactions including the processing of refunds as well as cash and card payments.
- Manage employee training for all new employees, where I offered continuous advice, guidance, and mentorship on duties and best practices.
- Responsible for greeting and serving customers as they entered the store and advising them on products and services available.
- Address customer service complaints while maintaining a friendly and calm demeanor.
- Attention to detail while displaying products at their best and keeping the shop floor clean and tidy.
- Accustomed to preforming tasks with high energy for shifts spanning 8 to 10 hours.
- Maintain a clean and neat appearance while at work.
- Receive, unpack, and place incoming merchandise on the shop floor.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

September 2017 — May 2021

Technological University Dublin

Final GPA - 3.0 (2:1)

Modules studied: Applied Artificial Intelligence and Deep Learning (**C+**), Enterprise Performance Architecture (**B+**), IT Governance and Quality (**B-**), Project (**B**), Interactive Media Design (**B+**), Information Management (**C+**), Social Media Analysis (**A**), Data Analysis and Programming (**C+**), Applied Machine Learning (**B-**).

PROJECTS

Final year project:

Emotion detection through image classification.

Leigh Warner

- Data selection and preparation of images to expand the dataset for further development of the network.
- Training the data using Python's built-in libraries such as **Tensor Flow**, **Pandas**, **NumPy**, and **SKLearn**.
- Development and fine tuning of **Convolutional Neural Networks** to gain the best models for predictions on unseen data.
- Use of pre-existing CNN models like **VGG-16**, **RESNET-**50, and **Inception-V3**. Predictions made on unseen data to allow models to accurately make predictions on the seven basic human emotions.
- Compared my own models to pre-existing models for comparison and made conclusions on overall best models

E-Commerce website project:

Vintage Vinyl Factory.

- This project consisted of a three-man team in which an e-commerce website was
 designed using UML, Play Framework, Scala, JavaScript, eBeans DB,
 Bootstrap, and JQuery.
- During the creation of the e-commerce site, bootstrap was used throughout for design and added functionality throughout the site.
- There was a **CRUD** system in place, which allowed for different levels of users to access the site e.g. administrator, manager, and a regular user.
- We implemented Stripe for our cart functionality, which allowed for fake transactions to occur to simulate real transactions taking place.
- The project was conducted within an **Agile** environment which included reporting to our supervisor each week on further developments within the project.

Map project:

Interactive Dublin map.

- Implemented HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Leaflet API to construct a website based on the clients desires and needs.
- Led weekly meetings with the client to update and demonstrate any progress that was made on the interactive map.
- Accepted feedback and modified the map according to the clients critiques and aesthetic preferences.
- Acquired new skills in networking, communication and coding through my own initiative.

SKILLS

- Coding languages Java, C++, Python, C#, SQL, PowerShell.
- Website design using HTML, CSS, APIs, JavaScript, Bootstrap.
- Efficient user of Windows and Linux operating systems.
- Understanding of **Machine Learning**, **Deep Learning** & **AI** models.
- Knowledge of AWS & Docker technologies.
- Capable user of cloud computing concepts such as **Networking**, **Routing**, **Switching**, **OSI model**, **Internet Protocol**, **Domain Name System**.

INTERESTS

- Keen interest in extreme sports.
- Participate in recording and performing live music.
- Film photography.

REFERENCES

References available upon request.

Leigh Warner 2